

Md. Kamrul Alam (Riyad)

ABOUT ME:

Near about 8 years+ experience in different reputed organizations, specialized in Sales & Engineering. I am accustomed to working in a challenging and fast-paced environment, particularly when dealing with multiple projects and priories at the same time.

--CONTACT--

) +8801670260025

@ riyadornobi@gmail.com

■ 1 No Building, R&H Staff Quarter, Mohakhali Taltola, Banany, Dhaka-1212

-- CORE KNOWLEDGE & SKILLED AREA--

- Core Knowledge:
- o Microsoft Office & Computing
- o Practical Skills
- o Expense Control

• Skilled Area:

- o Planning & Organizing
- o Strong Communication skills
- o Organizational Ability
- o Self-initiative/Decision Making
- o Problem solving/Analytical skills

--LANGUAGES--

Bangla: Native English: Good

Hindi: Speaking Only

--IT SKILLS--

MS Office

Hardware & Software Installations.

--INTERESTS--

Traveling, Music Cricket, Photography, Driving

----- Work Experience-----

> (01 May 2019 to Till now)

Advance Biometic

Senior Sales & Engineer.

Duties/Responsibilities:

- -Working Government sector and Private sector.
- -My products list:-
- OT Light, OT Table, Ultrasound, Color Doppler, Patients Monitoring System, ECG Machine, Suction Machine, Laboratory shaker Incubator, Hospital bed, Hospital Trolley, Patients monitors, Anesthesia system, CR machine, Pulse Oximeters, Liquid medical oxygen plant(VIE), Modern chemotherapy system, Biomedical safety cabinet.

Achievement:

- 1. Successfully sold many type of medical equipment & installed liquid oxygen plant in Cancer Hospital Mohakhali & National Hart Foundation Institute.
 - > 7 May 2017 to 30 April 2019:

Wills group.

Assistant Manager (Admin)

- Dealing with Local Govt. Authorities and Departments.
- Collect and preserve all company documents and make necessary to update them regularly.
- Look after office management and housekeeping.
- Make regular and sudden construction project visit.
- Handle some Recruitment for the office.

Achievement:

- 1. Successfully completed two years of service.
- > 10 October 2016 to 30 April 2017:
- 1 Asia alliance communication ltd.

Support Engineer

- Optical power management
- IPLC and IP transit service working principal.
- ODF firing and report reading and mapping.
- Transmission system related NMS.
- IP core related monitoring software:- Solar winds, Centrcon.
- Online UPS working principals.

-- EDUCATION --

> B.S.C Engineering Certificate:,

Atish Dipankar University of Science & Technology (ADUST).

Department: Electronic Telecommunication

Engineering,

Passing Year: 2012 CGPA: 3.00

Industrial Training : Teletalk Bangladesh Ltd.

Diploma Engineering Certificate

National Polytechnic Institute. Dhaka.

Department : Computer Engineering.

Passing Year : 2009 CGPA : 2.65

Board : Bangladesh Technical Education

Board, Dhaka.

Industrial Training: New Horizon.

Secondary School Certificate (SSC)

Passing Year : 2005

Name of Institution : Purbo Rampura High School.

Dhaka.

Department / Group : Business Studies.

CGPA : 2.94 Board : Dhaka

--PERSONAL INFORMATION--

Father:- Md. Sagir Ahemed

Mother:- Mrs. Ambia Begum

NID: 19872692616479187

Religion:- Islam

Date of Birth:- 17th April, 1989

Permanent Address: 254 East Gopalpur,

Monnu Nagar. Tongi, Gajipur.

Blood Group : B+

Achievement:

- 1. Successfully achieved ITC & IIG Networking acknowledgment.
- > 1st December 2011- 30th December 2012:

Ektoo Limited.

Support Engineer

- Monitoring Internet Connectivity of Bank & ATM booths.
- Handling Customer over phone.

Achievement:

1. Successfully handle all the customers.

-REFERENCE--

Ariful Hossain
Assistant General Manager
Accounts & Finance

1 Asia Alliansa Commun

1Asia Alliance Communication Ltd Email: ariful@1asia-ahl.com

A B M Khorshed Alam

Manager Administration

Wills Group

Plot# 35, Road# 46, Gulshan 2.

Mobile# 01677743607

Email# khorshedaru@gmail.com

-----Declaration-----

- I do hereby declare that the above information is true & correct to the best of my knowledge.
- Any additional information will be gladly provided upon request.

Md. Kamrul Alam (Riyad)